MIDNIGHT
[yawns]
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[narrator] Upon entering the palace,
Killua's first thought was…
who wasn't supposed to be
on the first floor,
standing right in front of them.
[Menthuthuyoupi] Who are these guys?
Where did they come from?
[narrator] Youpi was faced with
an implausible situation of his own,
but he simply ceased
all thought processes.
[flesh crackling]
My body is a shield.
As long as I stand, the King will be safe.
Perhaps because of this,
he cared less about his individual
identity than the other two.
This lack of ego became strength.
[narrator] Youpi smiled belligerently
and began transforming
as Shoot stood frozen in his tracks.
[narrator] It wasn't because Shoot
found himself psychologically defeated.
He knew…
[Shoot] If I move
any closer to him than this, he'll strike.
it came.
Huh?
[rumbling]
[Killua gasps]
Wait. This is the Dragon Dive!
So Netero's friend was…
[narrator] Only Killua understood
what was happening,
and it froze him on the spot.
[Killua] Seriously?
How in the hell did he realize that?
And so quickly in a situation like this?
Or, as Nen is known
to intensify after death,
would their bodies simply rot and decay
without ever being found?
No one knew the answer.
That meant that
in the worst-case scenario,
Gon!
[Morel] It's not Shoot's fault.
Even I didn't realize it
as quickly as Killua did.
[narrator] However, at that moment,
Shoot was experiencing
a completely different emotion.
[Shoot] Gon!
I want to scream it to the entire world!
That's Gon!
He's so much younger than me,
muffling even my own words
so that no one could hurt me.
I despised myself, but I couldn't fix it.
Friends and teachers gave me advice,
but I brushed it off
'cause they didn't have
those fears themselves.
They were strong.
But somehow…
[narrator] All of this was true.
Shoot did indeed shy away from everything.
[narrator] What Shoot failed to realize
was that
whenever he'd been faced with adversity,
that's when he truly came into his own.
[growls]
Hmm?
[groans]
-[Hunters gasping]
-[Gon grunts]
[Morel and Shoot] Knuckle and Meleoron…
[Gon and Killua] Are alive!
[Menthuthuyoupi] What?
Who the hell just attacked me?
[narrator] Of course
they verified beforehand
that Hakoware, Bankruptcy Chapter 7
would work with God's Accomplice.
As long as God's Accomplice was in play,
Youpi would be unable to see A.P.R.,
which means my focus right now should be…
[narrator] So far,
everything had proceeded according to plan
but even though
Knuckle succeeded in landing a blow,
he felt a chill run down his spine.
[Knuckle gasps]
Is this for real?
His aura is unlimited!
[narrator] A veteran
of over 5,000 battles,
Knuckle could quantify
his opponent's power
based on his experience and instinct.
And encountering a foe
with unprecedented powers
But there was no comparing the monster
that stood before him
with immense amounts of aura
to that of the countless opponents
he had faced before.
[Knuckle grunts]
Five times that of Morel?
Ten times? More?
[groans] I can't tell.
All right,
let's say he's ten times stronger,
with 700,000 aura.
Sure, he'd go bankrupt eventually.
But how long would that take?
[Neferpitou] Sire!
[narrator] Just then…
[Shaiapouf] Sire!
Sire!
[gasps]
[narrator] Since Pitou lacked wings,
the only option was to drop straight down.
However, in this instance,
that may actually have been fortunate.
Pitou would certainly have rushed
straight toward the King,
just as Pouf did.
would have had the presence of mind
to use En.
As a result…
[Neferpitou] The guest's quarters
are on the second floor of the west tower.
There. The King is with the blind woman.
[gasps]
[shudders]
They're also using En to locate the King!
[narrator] And it was then,
in that very moment,
that Pitou realized
the true gravity of their situation.
In an instant, Pitou crouched,
just as the four-legged ancestors
had done,
upper legs hard as steel
and swelled to twice the size
they had been during the battle with Kite.
All in order to reach the King
before the intruders could.
But only a second later…
[gasps]
[narrator] The destination
Pitou was traveling toward
began to emanate negative energy.
It was so strong that Pitou
immediately regretted this decision.
[Neferpitou] This is the King's.
[narrator] The aura coming from the King
was so unguarded
unimaginably and dramatically
in the wrong direction.
But all besides the King
were still frozen in time.
breath catching in their throats
at the sight before them,
a young girl covered in blood.
She rested in the arms
of a grotesque creature,
who, despite his appearance,
This only increased Pitou's uneasiness.
You will heal Komugi.
[narrator] Through all of this,
the two veterans
continued to stand in silence,
watching their enemies closely
as an expression of respect.
What was unfolding
was an act of love for another's life.
You know this isn't
what you told me I was signing up for.
[King] Not here.
We should do this somewhere else.
I believe a change of venue…
in order to separate the King
from the Royal Guards.
He had no reason
to object to the King's proposal.
it distracted the two men
for a split second,
a distraction for which
one could not blame them.
Their opponent
was an even greater monster.
[closing theme song playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, An Indebted Insect.
[Killua] Hey, what are you eating, Gon?
[Gon] Oh, these? They're gummi insects.
[Killua groans]
How can you eat those right now?
[singer singing in Japanese]